Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/tam-nguyen-van-968072100 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

docker
Kubernetes
Solution Architecture

Tam Nguyen Van

Al Engineer

Hanoi Capital Region

Summary

Experienced Project Manager Technical Lead with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Java, Computer Vision, C, and JavaScript. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Automatic Control from Hanoi university of Science and Technology.

Experience

VinoVoss Al FullIstack Engineer December 2023 - Present (1 year 4 months) Texas, United States

Immertec
FullIstack Engineer
September 2022 - December 2023 (1 year 4 months)
United States

InstillAI
AI FullIstack Engineer
June 2021 - December 2022 (1 year 7 months)
London Area, United Kingdom

Cinnamon Al Al Engineer October 2018 - June 2021 (2 years 9 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Panasonic R&D Center Vietnam
Project Manager/Technical Leader
April 2011 - October 2018 (7 years 7 months)
hanoi

Computer Vision, Mobile front-end development, sever-side development

Education

Hanoi university of Science and Technology Bachelor's Degree, Automatic Control · (2005 - 2011)